apracticalwedding.com 2017-02-04

# Privacy Policy - A Practical Wedding: We're Your Wedding Planner. Wedding Ideas for Brides, Bridesmaids, Grooms, and More

APW is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains APW’s guidelines concerning the use and the protection of your personal information, including our policies regarding what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. By using our site you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. From time to time, we may update this policy. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy on a regular basis to stay informed about how we use your personal information.

Personally Identifiable Information

We may request personally identifiable information (such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, e-mail address and/or any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of you). We only collect personal information from you if you voluntarily submit such information to us or our third party vendors. By submitting your personal information you give us permission to share the information with our partners and affiliates and to use such information for marketing or promotional purposes.

We will never intentionally disclose any personal information without permission. However, we may choose to release personal information to enforce our Terms of Use, manage our business, protect users or the general public, or to otherwise comply with legal obligations.

In event of a corporate change or a sale of our business we may share your personal information with another company.

Any User Content you leave on our site becomes public. We are not responsible for personal information you choose to include in your User Content. Although we strive to protect our users’ privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums and have no control over how such third parties may use your information. You disclose such information at your own risk.

In addition, on occasion, we may collect personal identification information from you in connection with optional contests, special offers or promotions. We will share such information with our partners, our affiliates and necessary third parties for the purpose of carrying out the contest, special offer or promotion. Your participation in the contest, special offer or promotion constitutes your consent to such disclosure and use of such information.

Nonpersonal Identification Information

Like many sites we use cookies or other technologies to improve your experience of our site. We or our third party vendors may collect nonpersonal information through the use of these technologies.

Nonpersonal information might include the browser you use, the type of computer you use and technical information about your means of connection to our site such as the operating systems and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. Our systems may also automatically gather information about the areas you visit and search terms you use on our site and about the links you may select from within our site to other areas of the Web or elsewhere online.

We may use such nonpersonal information for our business purposes and, in particular, primarily to administer the site, better manage advertising on the site and, in the aggregate, to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site. This way, we know which areas of our site are the favorites of our users, which areas need improvement and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our site.

Privacy of Children

The site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We prohibit children under the age of 13 for all interactive portions of the site, including our comment page. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we learn we have any information or content from anyone under the age of 13, we will delete that information.

Links to Other Sites

Users will find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies or no policy at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by APW.

Consent to Transfer

The site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our website, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

For more information on protecting your privacy, please visit www.ftc.gov/privacy.
